<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Field Expedient SDR</title>
    <link>localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Field Expedient SDR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>(c) 2016 Meadow Registry</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:54:23 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Field Expedient Linux</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/felinux/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:54:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/felinux/</guid>
      <description>David has also written a book explaining the Linux command line, called Field Expedient Linux. You can find out more at http://www.fieldlinux.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SDR Links</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:54:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/links/</guid>
      <description>More From Us Factoria Labs - http://www.factorialabs.com Field Expedient Linux - http://www.fieldlinux.com
gnuradio Installation Downloads and Info PyBombs GitHub - https://github.com/gnuradio/pybombs
SDR Hardware Links HackRF One - https://greatscottgadgets.com/hackrf/
Helpful Sites for Questions and Answers SDR tagged items on dsp.stackexchange - http://dsp.stackexchange.com/tags/sdr/hot SDR tagged items on electronics.stackexchange - http://electronics.stackexchange.com/tags/sdr/hot SDR tagged items on ham.stackexchange - http://ham.stackexchange.com/tags/sdr/hot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy The Books</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-au/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-au/</guid>
      <description>All volumes of the Field Expedient SDR series are available on [Amazon Australia] (http://www.amazon.com.au) in the Kindle format. We apologize for our inability to serve this market with a paperback format but hope you will enjoy the full-color ebook.
          Volume 1 Volume 2 Volume 3   [Kindle (full color)] (http://www.amazon.com.au/dp/B01M15DO0S) [Kindle (full color)] (http://www.amazon.com.au/dp/B01LXKJRSA) [Kindle (full color)] (http://www.amazon.com.au/dp/B01M15ECBR)         The links above are for purchase in Australia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy The Books</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-ca/</guid>
      <description>All volumes of the Field Expedient SDR series are available on [Amazon Canada] (http://www.amazon.ca) in paperback and Kindle formats. The paperbacks are available with a black and white interior as well as a full-color interior. Because the gnuradio interface color-codes some of its elements, there is additional value in the color versions. Unfortunately, the printing costs of full-color books are much more expensive, so we&amp;rsquo;ve also provided the more affordable black-and-white versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy The Books</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-de/</guid>
      <description>All volumes of the Field Expedient SDR series are available on [Amazon Germany] (http://www.amazon.de) in paperback and Kindle formats. The paperbacks are available with a black and white interior as well as a full-color interior. Because the gnuradio interface color-codes some of its elements, there is additional value in the color versions. Unfortunately, the printing costs of full-color books are much more expensive, so we&amp;rsquo;ve also provided the more affordable black-and-white versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy The Books</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-es/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-es/</guid>
      <description>All volumes of the Field Expedient SDR series are available on [Amazon Spain] (http://www.amazon.es) in paperback and Kindle formats. The paperbacks are available with a black and white interior as well as a full-color interior. Because the gnuradio interface color-codes some of its elements, there is additional value in the color versions. Unfortunately, the printing costs of full-color books are much more expensive, so we&amp;rsquo;ve also provided the more affordable black-and-white versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy The Books</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-fr/</guid>
      <description>All volumes of the Field Expedient SDR series are available on [Amazon France] (http://www.amazon.fr) in paperback and Kindle formats. The paperbacks are available with a black and white interior as well as a full-color interior. Because the gnuradio interface color-codes some of its elements, there is additional value in the color versions. Unfortunately, the printing costs of full-color books are much more expensive, so we&amp;rsquo;ve also provided the more affordable black-and-white versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy The Books</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-it/</guid>
      <description>All volumes of the Field Expedient SDR series are available on [Amazon Italy] (http://www.amazon.it) in paperback and Kindle formats. The paperbacks are available with a black and white interior as well as a full-color interior. Because the gnuradio interface color-codes some of its elements, there is additional value in the color versions. Unfortunately, the printing costs of full-color books are much more expensive, so we&amp;rsquo;ve also provided the more affordable black-and-white versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy The Books</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-jp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-jp/</guid>
      <description>All volumes of the Field Expedient SDR series are available on [Amazon Japan] (http://www.amazon.jp) in the Kindle format. We apologize for our inability to serve this market with a paperback format but hope you will enjoy the full-color ebook.
          Volume 1 Volume 2 Volume 3   [Kindle (full color)] (http://www.amazon.jp/dp/B01M15DO0S) [Kindle (full color)] (http://www.amazon.jp/dp/B01LXKJRSA) [Kindle (full color)] (http://www.amazon.jp/dp/B01M15ECBR)         The links above are for purchase in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy The Books</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/buy-region/buy-uk/</guid>
      <description>All volumes of the Field Expedient SDR series are available on [Amazon UK] (http://www.amazon.co.uk) in paperback and Kindle formats. The paperbacks are available with a black and white interior as well as a full-color interior. Because the gnuradio interface color-codes some of its elements, there is additional value in the color versions. Unfortunately, the printing costs of full-color books are much more expensive, so we&amp;rsquo;ve also provided the more affordable black-and-white versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy The Books</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/buy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:54:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/buy/</guid>
      <description>All volumes of the Field Expedient SDR series are available on [Amazon] (http://www.amazon.com/?tag=fieldxp_web-20) in paperback and Kindle formats. The paperbacks are available with a black and white interior as well as a full-color interior. Because the gnuradio interface color-codes some of its elements, there is additional value in the color versions. Unfortunately, the printing costs of full-color books are much more expensive, so we&amp;rsquo;ve also provided the more affordable black-and-white versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact the Authors</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:53:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>Both authors provide consulting services as well as training classes for SDR. For more information, please see the [Factoria Labs] (http://www.factorialabs.com) web site, or contact us at the following address:
 email: sdr&amp;lt;at&amp;gt;factorialabs.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing gnuradio</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 22:52:46 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/install/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE:
The installation instructions in the books are now completely out of date and do not support the most recent version of Ubuntu. Rather than provide a new set of instructions, we&amp;rsquo;ve simplified things by creating an installation script that handles almost everything. Please see the following post for details:
[Updated gnuradio Install Instructions] (https://factorialabs.com/2020/01/11/updated-gnuradio-install-instructions-2/)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downloads</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/downloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 17:52:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/downloads/</guid>
      <description>Each book in the Field Expedient SDR Series walks through a host of exercises. Below you can download a single *.tar.gz file for each book. Each file contains all of the completed exercises and raw data files referenced in its associated book. You should download the file to a convenient location and then run the following command:
tar -xvzf &amp;lt;filename&amp;gt;  The files are broken down into folders for each chapter, and the top level contains a text file called &amp;ldquo;project_list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Field Expedient SDR Series</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 16:41:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>First some comments from fans of the series:
  There is a whole world out there waiting for you.
A world not seen by many people. This book opens the world of SDR to the masses and makes it approachable, fun and useful. It is required reading for all Black Hills Information Security team members.
John Strand Owner - Black Hills InfoSec Senior Instructor for SANS
   If you are looking for a practical, top down approach for GNURadio and SDR proficiency, this series is precisely what you&amp;rsquo;re looking for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Field Expedient SDR</title>
      <link>localhost:1313/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 16:41:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/home/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Field Expedient SDR web site. Here you can learn about the books and check out the latest gnuradio installation guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>localhost:1313/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>localhost:1313/license/</guid>
      <description>This website was generated using the [Hugo] (https://gohugo.io/) static web page toolset. Further, it used the [hyde-y] (https://github.com/enten/hyde-y) theme, which is licensed per the terms below.
The MIT License (MIT)
Copyright (c) 2015 Steven Enten
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
